<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 2 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f4f8fb; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>8.5. Application Form:</b><br>
      Each applicant is required to fill an application form, for the positions advertised, which is provided free of cost by the HR Department (Specimen attached as per Annex “A”). 
      This application form must be filled by the applicant himself and must reach on or before the prescribed date to the HR Section. 
      The form comprises four sections:
      <ul>
        <li>Personal Data</li>
        <li>Education Qualification</li>
        <li>Experience Details</li>
        <li>Skills possessed by the individual</li>
      </ul>
      <i>Note: In case of support staff, application form is not mandatory.</i>
      <br><br>

      <b>8.6. Long Listing:</b><br>
      After advertisement, applicants send their resume and covering letter through email or courier. 
      The HR Department creates a pool of candidates, sorts applications/CVs, and prepares the long listing to share with the concerned Head of Department for short listing.
      <br><br>

      <b>8.7. Short Listing:</b><br>
      The Head of Department, facilitated by HR, evaluates long-listed resumes on the basis of experience, qualification, gender, age, and set criteria. 
      Suitable candidates are invited for test/interview. 
      The HR Committee validates the short listing, then finalizes and sends it to HR for further process.
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock2').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock2" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 2 of 9</b><br><br>
      According to NIDA-Pak’s recruitment process, which of the following statements is correct?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      The application form is mandatory for advertised posts (except support staff) and must be completed by the applicant, while short listing is validated by the HR Committee.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Application forms may be filled by anyone on behalf of the applicant, and the HR Committee does not review the short listing.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Long listing is prepared directly by the Head of Department without involvement of the HR Department.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Support staff are always required to fill the application form without exception.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! For advertised positions, applicants must complete the application form themselves (except support staff), and the HR Committee validates the short listing prepared with HR’s facilitation.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Sorry, that’s not correct. The correct statement is that applicants must personally fill the application form (except for support staff), and the HR Committee validates the short listing.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one item only.</partial>
</content>
