<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 1 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f4f8fb; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>8.3. Emergency Recruitment (Walk-in or Fast-Track):</b><br>
      In emergency or humanitarian response situations, NIDA-Pak may adopt expedited recruitment methods such as walk-in interviews or headhunting to ensure rapid deployment of qualified staff. 
      Safeguards will be applied to ensure accountability and compliance with minimum standards.
      <br><br>
      <b>8.4. General Recruitment Conditions:</b><br>
      The recruitment policy of NIDA-Pak gives the following conditions for recruitment:
      <ul>
        <li>The minimum employment age is 18 years.</li>
        <li>All applicants must meet the qualifications and experience as stated in the job description.</li>
        <li>Reference and background checks are mandatory before final appointment.</li>
      </ul>
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock1').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock1" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 1 of 9</b><br><br>
      Under NIDA-Pak’s recruitment policy, which of the following statements is correct?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      Emergency recruitment can be conducted through walk-in interviews, but all applicants must still meet minimum qualifications and undergo background checks.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      In emergency recruitment, NIDA-Pak may waive minimum qualifications and background checks to speed up hiring.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      The minimum employment age can be relaxed in emergencies to allow faster recruitment.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Reference checks are optional during humanitarian response recruitment drives.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! Even in emergency recruitment situations, NIDA-Pak requires candidates to meet the minimum qualifications and to undergo reference and background checks to ensure accountability.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Sorry, that’s not correct. The correct answer is that emergency recruitment may use walk-in methods, but qualifications and background checks are still mandatory under NIDA-Pak’s policy.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one item only.</partial>
</content>
