<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 5 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f4f9fd; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>9. Employee Orientation:</b><br>
      NIDA-Pak provides orientation for all new employees regarding organizational policies and procedures. 
      The concerned department head is responsible for conducting orientation, while employees are expected 
      to study policies thoroughly. Orientation provides an overview of departmental functioning and encourages 
      employees to ask questions. Upon completion, the employee signs an acknowledgement which is retained by HR. 
      (Specimen attached as per Annex “F”).
      <br><br>

      <b>10. Training and Management Development:</b><br>
      Training is a planned attempt to facilitate employee learning of job-related knowledge, skills, and behaviors. 
      Development focuses on preparing employees for future responsibilities. Training may be internal or external, 
      usually after the probation period, and is recommended by the Line Manager and validated by HR, subject to 
      Training Needs Assessment (TNA). (Specimen attached as per Annex “G”).
      <br><br>

      <b>10.1 Employee Training:</b><br>
      The NIDA-Pak training center is located at the Head Office, providing comprehensive instruction across major 
      fields using various training and development techniques.
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock5').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock5" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 5 of 9</b><br><br>
      Which of the following best describes NIDA-Pak’s approach to employee orientation and training?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      Orientation is conducted by the department head and acknowledged by the employee, while training is recommended after probation and validated by HR through a Training Needs Assessment.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Orientation is optional and handled by HR only, while training is provided immediately after hiring with no assessment required.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Employees are expected to train themselves, while orientation is only provided for senior management staff.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Training is mandatory before the probation period ends, and orientation acknowledgements are not kept in HR records.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! Orientation is led by the department head and formally acknowledged by employees, while training opportunities 
    are based on probation completion, supervisor recommendation, and HR-validated Training Needs Assessment.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Sorry, that’s not correct. The correct answer is that orientation is conducted by the department head and signed off 
    by employees, and training is offered after probation, validated through TNA.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one item only.</partial>
</content>
