<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 6 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#fdf9f4; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>11. On-the-Job Training:</b><br>
      On-the-job training is provided to existing or newly appointed employees to update their knowledge of procedures, rules, and sector developments. 
      Employees may also be nominated for external training on the recommendation of their supervisor, HR, and with the CEO’s final approval.
      <br><br>

      <b>12. Management Development:</b><br>
      NIDA-Pak improves managerial performance by imparting knowledge, shaping attitudes, and enhancing skills. 
      Managers are exposed to learning opportunities while performing their duties.
      <br><br>

      <b>13. Succession Planning:</b><br>
      NIDA-Pak identifies and develops staff with potential to fill senior-level positions in the future, ensuring the availability of capable employees 
      for leadership roles as they arise.
      <br><br>

      <b>14. Job Rotation:</b><br>
      Job rotation broadens employee experience by allowing them to work in different roles, identifying strengths and weaknesses. 
      Salary adjustments may be applied temporarily when employees rotate into higher or project-based roles. 
      Employees must complete assigned tasks before the rotation takes effect.
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock6').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock6" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 6 of 9</b><br><br>
      Which of the following best reflects NIDA-Pak’s approach to staff development and capacity building?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Only external training is provided, and job rotation is not part of the organization’s capacity-building approach.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Succession planning is optional, and management development is only conducted when vacancies are available.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Employees must rely solely on self-study and personal initiative for training and development at NIDA-Pak.
    </option>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      NIDA-Pak uses on-the-job training, management development, succession planning, and job rotation to enhance skills, prepare future leaders, and broaden employee experience.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! NIDA-Pak combines on-the-job training, management development, succession planning, and job rotation to build skills, 
    strengthen management, and prepare capable staff for future leadership roles.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Sorry, that’s not correct. The correct answer is that NIDA-Pak emphasizes on-the-job training, management development, 
    succession planning, and job rotation as key methods for employee development and capacity building.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one item only.</partial>
</content>
