<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 7 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f9fbf4; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>15. Job Enlargement:</b><br>
      Job enlargement means increasing the scope of a job by extending its duties and responsibilities. 
      It motivates employees, enhances productivity, builds capacity, and reduces boredom. 
      Additional salary may sometimes be provided depending on the nature of the task, but it is not compulsory.
      <br><br>

      <b>16. Behavior Modeling:</b><br>
      NIDA-Pak provides training on behavioral modeling, which focuses on developing employee behavioral and interpersonal skills. 
      This is done by demonstrating management techniques through videos and displays, followed by role-playing exercises 
      in simulated situations.
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock7').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock7" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 7 of 9</b><br><br>
      Which of the following statements best reflects NIDA-Pak’s approach to <em>Job Enlargement</em> and <em>Behavior Modeling</em>?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      Job enlargement extends duties to increase motivation and productivity, while behavior modeling develops interpersonal skills through demonstrations and role-playing.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Job enlargement only increases salaries, and behavior modeling focuses solely on technical skills.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Job enlargement reduces workload, and behavior modeling is based on employee self-study.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Both job enlargement and behavior modeling require external trainers only.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! Job enlargement increases the scope of duties to boost motivation and productivity, 
    while behavior modeling strengthens interpersonal and behavioral skills through demonstrations and role-play.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Not quite. The correct answer is that NIDA-Pak uses job enlargement to expand duties and build capacity, 
    and behavior modeling to develop interpersonal skills using demonstrations and simulations.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one option only.</partial>
</content>
