<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 8 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f4f9fd; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>17. Remunerations, Expenses, Loan and Taxes:</b><br>
      Regular and contractual employees shall draw their pay, allowances, and fringe benefits as stated in their letter of appointment, 
      subject to the terms and conditions mentioned. Salaries are paid on the last day of each month in Pakistani Rupees, 
      through bank transfer or cheque.
      <br><br>

      <b>17.1. Payment of Tax:</b><br>
      <ul>
        <li>Employees are responsible for paying taxes; however, income tax is calculated on the estimated annual liability and deducted monthly.</li>
        <li>The deducted amount is deposited into the government treasury under prevailing tax law.</li>
        <li>While employees must file their own tax returns, NIDA-Pak’s Finance Section may assist in completing forms.</li>
        <li>Any new taxes imposed by the Government shall be dealt with in line with tax laws.</li>
      </ul>
      <br>

      <b>17.2. 13th Month Salary:</b><br>
      <ul>
        <li>Salaries are paid on a 13-month basis.</li>
        <li>The 13th month salary is granted to every regular employee completing one year of service.</li>
        <li>It equals one basic monthly salary (excluding overtime, bonus, or allowances).</li>
        <li>It is paid in two instalments: one before Eid-ul-Fitr or other religious events, and the second on Eid-ul-Azha or with December salary, subject to availability of funds/budget.</li>
      </ul>
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock8').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock8" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 8 of 9</b><br><br>
      What is the correct understanding of NIDA-Pak’s remuneration and taxation policies, including the 13th month salary?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      Salaries are paid monthly in PKR, income tax is deducted and deposited by NIDA-Pak while employees file returns, and a 13th month salary is paid in two instalments to regular staff completing one year of service.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Salaries are paid quarterly, tax filing is handled entirely by NIDA-Pak, and the 13th month salary is an additional bonus based on performance.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Employees receive salaries in foreign currency, taxes are optional, and the 13th month salary is given only when approved by supervisors.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      NIDA-Pak pays salaries on a 12-month basis only, with no provision for a 13th month, and employees manage all tax deductions independently.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! NIDA-Pak ensures monthly salary payments in PKR, deducts and deposits income tax as per law, assists with tax forms, 
    and provides a 13th month salary in two instalments to eligible staff.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Not correct. The policy states that NIDA-Pak deducts income tax monthly, assists with filing, and provides a 13th month salary 
    (equal to basic pay) in two instalments to regular employees who have completed one year of service.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one option only.</partial>
</content>
