<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 4 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f9fdf4; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>8.11. Emergency Waivers:</b><br>
      In emergency situations or cases of urgent need, the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) may waive formal recruitment and selection procedures. Under this provision, NIDA-Pak may:
      <ul>
        <li>Circulate certain new positions internally only.</li>
        <li>Shift duties of a regular/contract employee to another department, region, or project without advertisement, test, or interview.</li>
        <li>Assign additional charge to a regular/contract employee without advertisement, test, or interview.</li>
        <li>Seek and re-hire ex-employees of NIDA-Pak without advertisement.</li>
        <li>Recruit directly from the CV bank or via headhunting without advertisement.</li>
      </ul>
      <br>

      <b>8.12. Probation Period:</b><br>
      The first three months of employment for regular/permanent staff are considered a probationary period. For contract or temporary employees, probation may vary or may not apply depending on project duration. At the end of probation:
      <ul>
        <li>Performance is reviewed by the supervisor and management.</li>
        <li>Extension or confirmation depends on a written recommendation by the supervisor.</li>
        <li>If performance is unsatisfactory, a written plan with a timetable for improvement is initiated.</li>
        <li>Employment may be terminated at any time during the probation period.</li>
      </ul>
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock4').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock4" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 4 of 9</b><br><br>
      Which of the following statements correctly reflects NIDA-Pak’s policy on emergency waivers and probation?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      The CEO may waive recruitment steps in emergencies, and probationary employees may be terminated at any time within the probation period if performance is unsatisfactory.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Only the HR Department can waive recruitment procedures, and all probationary employees must complete three months before termination is possible.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Emergency waivers are limited to ex-employee rehiring, and probationary reviews are optional at the discretion of the supervisor.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Employees on probation cannot be terminated until the final day of the probationary period, regardless of performance.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! In emergencies, the CEO may bypass normal recruitment procedures, and during probation, employees can be reviewed, extended, or terminated depending on performance and supervisor recommendations.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Sorry, that’s not correct. The correct answer is that the CEO may waive formal recruitment in emergencies, and probationary employees can be terminated at any time if their performance is unsatisfactory.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one item only.</partial>
</content>
