<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content marked="false" checkText="I'm done" showText="Show me" instructionsText="Instructions" titleText="Recruitment Policy Assessment 9 of 9" closeText="OK">
  <instructions>
    Read the recruitment policy narrative carefully. When ready, click the "Check Your Knowledge" button to reveal the question and answer choices. 
    Then select the correct response and choose "I'm done" to check your answers.
  </instructions>

  <!-- Narration -->
  <question>
    <![CDATA[
    <div style="border:1px solid #999; background:#f4f9fd; padding:12px; margin-bottom:15px; border-radius:6px; font-family:Arial; font-size:14px; line-height:1.5;">
      <b>17.3. Salary Revision:</b><br>
      NIDA-Pak may revise regular employees’ salaries annually based on inflation, market price assessments, and organizational budget. The percentage increase applies to the basic salary of each eligible staff.
      <br><br>

      <b>17.4. Advances:</b><br>
      <ul>
        <li><b>17.4.1 Advances on Salaries:</b> Employees may request an advance before the 10th of each month, limited to 50% of monthly salary, payable on the 15th.</li>
        <li><b>17.4.2 Professional Advances:</b> Employees are responsible for all professional advances for organizational operations. Advances must be cleared weekly or before leave. Only one professional advance at a time is allowed. Outstanding advances are settled upon contract termination; missing amounts are deducted, and legal action may be taken if reimbursement is refused.</li>
      </ul>
      <br>

      <b>18. Expenses and Loans:</b><br>
      <ul>
        <li>All business-related expenses must be pre-approved in writing by the line manager to qualify for reimbursement.</li>
        <li>NIDA-Pak does not provide loans to employees.</li>
      </ul>
    </div>

    <!-- Reveal button -->
    <div style="margin-top:15px; text-align:center;">
      <button onclick="document.getElementById('qaBlock9').style.display='block'; this.style.display='none';" 
              style="background:#0066cc; color:#fff; padding:10px 20px; border:none; border-radius:6px; font-size:14px; cursor:pointer;">
        Check Your Knowledge
      </button>
    </div>

    <!-- Hidden wrapper where LMS injects the answers -->
    <div id="qaBlock9" style="display:none; margin-top:20px;">
      <b>Recruitment Policy Assessment 9 of 9</b><br><br>
      Which of the following best summarizes NIDA-Pak’s policies on salary revision, advances, expenses, and loans?
    </div>
    ]]>
  </question>

  <!-- Let LMS handle answers outside CDATA -->
  <answers>
    <option correct="1" display_order="0">
      Salaries are revised annually based on inflation and budget, salary advances can be requested within limits, professional advances must be cleared promptly, business expenses require prior approval, and NIDA-Pak does not provide loans.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="1">
      Salaries are fixed, employees can request unlimited advances, expenses do not require approval, and loans may be granted on special occasions.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="2">
      Salary revisions depend solely on performance reviews, advances are optional, and NIDA-Pak provides loans under management discretion.
    </option>
    <option correct="0" display_order="3">
      Employees manage all advances independently, expenses are reimbursed without approval, and salary revision is decided every two years.
    </option>
  </answers>

  <!-- Feedback -->
  <correct audio="">
    Correct! NIDA-Pak revises salaries annually, regulates advances responsibly, requires prior approval for expenses, and does not grant loans, ensuring accountability and financial discipline.
  </correct>
  <incorrect audio="">
    Not correct. The correct policy states that salaries may be revised annually, salary and professional advances are regulated, business expenses require pre-approval, and loans are not provided.
  </incorrect>
  <partial audio="">Select one option only.</partial>
</content>
